Guide to the Don Byrd Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual materials, 1960s-1990s; 5; 3; (3 boxes)
  - Audiocassettes, 1970s-1990s
    - Palmer, Michael. Johnson, Ronald. Levi Strauss, David. "Syntax as Music, on Zukofsky, Small Press Distribution, Berkeley", 1988 April 22; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972373)
    - Olson, Charles. "Goddard College, Maximus V", undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972530)
    - Ashbery, John. Yau, John. "Albany", 1984 February 25; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972548)
    - Duncan, Robert. "Bard College", 1983 April 12; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972555)
    - Duncan, Robert. "Bard College, Lecture on H.D.", 1983 April 26; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972563)
    - Lansing, Gerrit. "John Ashbery introduction. Bard College", 1995 November 17; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972571)
    - Funkhouser, Chris., 1992 November 5; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972589)
    - Stein, Charles. "Alchemy", 1990 February 27; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972597)
    - Dorn, Ed. "Albany", 1980 April 15; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972605)
    - Duncan, Robert. "Bard College", 1982 October 14; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972613)
    - Mac Low, Jackson. "Albany", 1984 November 26; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972621)
    - Irby, Ken. "Albany", undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972670)
    - Mac Low, Jackson., 1984 November1; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972662)
    - Metcalf, Paul. "Reading from Golden Delicious", 1983 March 19; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972654)
    - Duncan, Robert. "Albany and elsewhere", undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972647)
    - Bernstein, Charles. "Class" / Stein, Charles. "from theforestforthetrees", Widemouth Tapes, undated, 1982 March; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002109972639)
    - Chadabe, Joel. "With Pierre's Words, Pierre Joris, recitation and poem", 1997 May 3; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109972985)
    - Olson, Charles. "Causal Myth, Robert Duncan introduction, Berkeley" / James Joyce, Finnegan's Wake", 1965; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109972993)
    - Sanders, Ed. "Maximus from Dogtown-I, performed at Berkeley Olson Festival", 1991 February 23; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973009)
      Inscribed and signed by Sanders to Don Byrd
    - Sun Ra. "Trudie Morse reading otherwise unavailable Sun Ra poems at Soundscape", undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973017)
      A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
      Side A / Side B
      Astro Black
      Where There's No Sun
      Living in the Space Age
      [?] Eggs Sunny Side Up
      0-27
      Watusi
      Space is the [Place?]
      We Travel the Sky Ways
      On Jupiter
      From Astro Black
    - Blaser, Robin. "Charles Olson lecture #1" (1 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973033)
    - Blaser, Robin. "Charles Olson lecture #2" (2 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973025)
    - Blaser, Robin. "Charles Olson lecture #3" (3 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973041)
    - "Talkwork: Performance Quarterly, issue no. 3", 1991; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973058)
    - Hennix, Christer. "Charles Stein Parmenides", 1984 July 28; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973066)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don., 1994 October 5; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973074)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don.; G— Keane (?), "day #10" (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1987 March 10; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973090)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don.; G— Keane (?), "day #11" (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1987 March 10; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973082)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don., 1987 January 7; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973108)
    - Coolidge, Clark. Byrd, Don. (3), 1989 November 8, December 11; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973116)
    - Coolidge, Clark. Byrd, Don. (1), 1989 January 30, February 9; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973124)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don., 1997 February 7; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973132)
    - Stein, Charles. "Discussion with Don Byrd", 1980 April 30; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973140)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don. "Catskill, N.Y." (1 of 3 cassettes), 1994 September 14; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973157)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don. "Catskill, N.Y." (2 of 3 cassettes), 1994 September 14; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973165)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don. "Catskill, N.Y.," (3 of 3 cassettes), 1994 September 14; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973173)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don. "Rhinebeck, Poughkeepsie" (1 of 2 microcassettes), 1992 March 25; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973215)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don. "Rhinebeck, Poughkeepsie" (2 of 2 microcassettes), 1992 March 25; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973223)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don. "Woodstock, N.Y.", 1995 March 15; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973231)
    - Brakhage, Stan. "Union", 1992 April 16; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973249)
    - Blaser, Robin. "Lecture, Vancouver", 1995 June; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973181)
    - Stein, Charles, Byrd, Don. Ryan., 1994 September 21; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973199)
    - "AE's internview with Charles Stein, Bard College", 1991 September 29; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973207)
    - Stein, Charles. Byrd, Don., 1995 Spring; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002109973256)
- Printed materials, 1970-2007; 2; (2 boxes)
  - Printed materials, 1970-2007 (Box A)
  - Printed materials, 1970-2007 (Box B)